The people are seeing it. Alright, so keep
watching this video and I'm going to walk
you through pretty much what you should be
observing, looking out for, and keeping up
to date with if you want to be a part of
this bull cycle and be a part of these
gains during this market upcoming into the
new year. Alright, hit that like button,
subscribe, get us to a thousand subs man,
and I hope you guys are having a great
day, a great month, you know, ready to end
this year off right and be in a better
position to start the new year.
Alright y'all, so AI in the blockchain
man, right now we are at a pivotal moment
that everybody should be pretty much
focused on, right? Like we got agents, we
got codecs, we got, you know, cartoons, we
got, you know, people using AI to
basically be their, you know, planner,
their thinker, their marketer. So many
things is happening in this space.
However, I want you to focus on how these
tools can help you. If you are not a
creator, if you're not a graphic designer,
if you're not a coder, a builder, you
don't have to think too much of the
complexities. But what you do have to
think about is how you can incorporate
these tools to assist you. Are you a
parent who has children, but you have
dreams, you have some ideas you want to
work on? Use AI. Are you a child that is
struggling with some topics you want to
learn? You want to, you know, be more
informed, you want to, you know, pass your
classes and stuff? Use AI to help you
understand. Not to make, not to, not for
you to replace whatever you have to do and
give it to AI, but help it to collaborate
and enhance your already thinking, right?
The blockchain in this technology is not
going anywhere. It's going to get faster
and more advanced, if anything, right? But
we have to figure out how we can use these
tools in our lives. Not how we can chase
and do everything that everybody else is
doing, because that's just going to like
leave you chasing something. Find out if
you're a teacher, how can you use AI to
help your lessons plan and, you know, be
more specific to your students, right? So
teachers, regular nine to five workers,
anybody for real, for real, you know, you
want to start learning these tools, you
know, INNERG INTEL is geared towards
that is to help the next generation of
thinkers of, you know, business owners and
help them get prepared to use these tools
and become, you know, essentially AI
native in 2026 and moving forward. We're
closer to 2030. And if you have not
learned or dive into this AI space on any
level, you are falling behind. So, you
know, take the time to keep watching this
video, go back on this video to start to
learn about the different tools like
Codex, like Hermes, like, you know,
Claude, you know, these are models and,
you know, harnesses that you can use and
build agents with. Grok, you know, a
Twitter is building their own agent. So
there's so many resources, you know, that
you can use and tap into going YouTube, so
many videos on, you know, these agents, I
put up a video on OpenClaw. I built my
second brain and claw, you know, agent. If
you have any questions about that, feel
free to reach out and I can help you set
up yours or, you know, see how any of
these agents can help you. But we must
start to think a little faster. A lot of
this stuff is flying by under our radars
with none of us having the knowledge, the
conversations. If you want to stay ahead,
if you want to get ahead, tap into the AI
blockchain ecosystems. Right. I got a sub
stack. I put a lot of my stuff on
subscribe to the YouTube. And if you are
interested in hands on, I will be
releasing more information on my agent
Academy, because I am teaching, you know,
other developers and other founders on how
to become AI native as well. So that's
you. Come on. And, you know, like this
video up and tap into the system.
So DCA, right? A lot of people, you know,
as I was starting trading and sharing
information, people would say, well,
what's your strategy? What's your
strategy? Now, there's so many different
strategies you can use.